

Juan Serrato

Web Developer

O in

ABOUT ME

EXPEREINCE

EDUCATION

ABOUT ME

Hello, My name is Juan Serrato. I am an IT Engineer focused on software developer, my greatest expertise is in development. I am passionate about technology like a geek, on the other hand I love nature

Full Name: Juan Manuel Serrato Naranjo

Birthday: Octuber 07, 1993

Location: La Piedad, Mich., Mex.

Email: juanserrato100@gmail.com

Phone: 352 105-1557

Web Development Mobile Hybrid

UX/UI Back-End

EXPERIENCE

Glouu Technologies

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | AUGUST, 2017 - PRESENT

Analysis, design, development and testing of solutions.

- Front-End Development: Javascript, Angular, ReactJS, NextJS, VueJS, HTML, CSS, SASS
- Mobile Development: Ionic, React Native
- Back-End Development: NodeJS, ExpressJS, Java, Spring Boot
- Data Base: MySQL, SQL Server, MongoDB, Firebase
- Other: NPM, GIT, Webpack, Adobe XD, Cypress, Scrum, Conekta

SYE Software

FRONTEND DEVELOPER | APRIL 2017 - AUGUST, 2017

Design and development of web Interfaces

- **Development:** Javascript, Angular, HTML, CSS
- Other: NPM, GIT, Webpack, Scrum, JIRA

Girasolo

IT DIRECTOR | FEBRUARY 2016 - APRIL 2017

Responsible for analysis, estimate, design and development of Software Solutions

- Development: Javascript, JQuery, PHP, Laravel, HTML, CSS
- Data Base: MySQL
- Other: GIT, PhotoShop, Trello

EDUCATION

ENGINEERING ICTs

JANUARY 2011 - DECEMBER 2016

INSTITUTO TECNOLÓGICO DE LA PIEDAD

PLATZI

APRIL, 2021